transcribeme.com 2019-08-27

# Privacy Policy - TranscribeMe!

The following Privacy Policy applies to our data collection and use practices relating to your use of the TranscribeMe services, our website and our other products and services (collectively, the “TranscribeMe Services”). As a TranscribeMe registrant or visitor you agree to this Privacy Policy and also to any further modifications made to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply, however, to the co-branded pages of our partners, affiliates and service providers. The terms “TranscribeMe”, “we”, “our”, or “us” refer to TranscribeMe Inc.

TranscribeMe may enter into written product or service agreements with business customers that contain specific provisions related to the confidentiality, security or other handling of information. When provisions of a written product or service agreement differ from or conflict with the provisions of this Privacy Policy, the terms of the written agreement will apply. In all other instances, the terms of this Policy apply.

The Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this website and its related services, and will notify you of the following:

**1\. Information Collection, Use and Sharing:**  
What personal and non-personal information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.

**2\. Cookies and Your Control Over Them**

**3\. Your Control Over Your Data:**  
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.

**4\. Your Access to Your Data:**  
How you may access your data.

**5\. Securing Your Data:**  
What security measures are in place to prevent the misuse of your information.

**6\. Contacting Us:**  
How you can contact us regarding any inaccuracies in the information.

### **1\. Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

TranscribeMe Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. When you request information or content from TranscribeMe and supply information or content that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you, you agree to share that information with TranscribeMe, its agents, representatives, and affiliates. We only collect or have access to information that you voluntarily give us via our online portal, marketing site, mobile app or related tools. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. 

TranscribeMe, Inc. requests information from you on our online portal, mobile app, marketing site or related tools. To order transcription services, you must provide contact information (i.e. name and email) and financial information (i.e. credit card number). This information is used for billing purposes and to process your transcription orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you.

TranscribeMe, Inc. may use your personal information to respond to you regarding your order. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization or with any other users of our services. All associates and trusted parties of TranscribeMe, Inc. who assist in operating our business and services have signed Non-Disclosure Agreements (NDAs) to keep all transcription data confidential. 

Some other instances where we may also release your information would be when we have to comply with the law, enforce our website/business policies, or protect our or others rights, property, or safety. Also, when the information is pursuant to court orders or law enforcement request (i.e. search warrant, subpoena, court order, discovery request). Otherwise, personally identifiable visitor information will not be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Additionally, we will never disclose any personally identifiable or financial information related to payment activities. 

By voluntarily entering personally identifiable information on our website, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Before this information is submitted to our systems you must acknowledge your understanding of this Policy. You acknowledge and agree that such personal data may be transferred from your current location to our servers located within the United States. TranscribeMe’s services are not intended for use by children, and we do not knowingly collect or store any personal information about children under the age of 13.

### **2\. Cookies and Your Control Over Them**

Cookies are small text files which are transferred from our websites, applications or services and stored on your device. We use cookies to help us provide you with a personalized service, and to improve the user-experience on our websites, applications and services.

Our cookies may be session cookies (temporary cookies that identify and track users within our websites, applications or services that are deleted when you close your browser or leave your session in the application or service) or persistent cookies (cookies which enable our websites, applications or services to remember who you are and your preferences within our websites, applications or services, including those that will stay on your computer or device after you close your browser or leave your session in the application or service).

We use the following different types of cookies:  
**Strictly necessary cookies**  
These are are needed for our websites, applications or services to function properly. For example, these cookies allow you to access secure areas of our website or to remember what you have put into your shopping cart.  
**Performance cookies and analytics technologies**  
These collect information about how users navigate our websites, applications and services, for instance which functionality visitors use most often. They don’t collect information that identifies a visitor or user. We only use these cookies to improve how our website, applications and services work, so all information collected is anonymous.  
**Functionality cookies**  
These allow our websites, applications and services to remember choices you make (such as your username, language or country) and provide enhanced, more personal features. They can also be used to remember changes you have made to services and other parts of web pages that you can customize. The information these collect may be anonymized and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.  
**IP Address and traffic data**  
We keep a record of traffic data which is logged automatically by our servers, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, and device information. We also collect some site, application and service statistics such as access rates, page hits and page views. We are not able to identify any individual from traffic data or site statistics. 

**Google Analytics** uses “cookies” to help the website analyze how users use the websites, applications or services. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the websites, applications or services (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the websites, applications or services compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser or within the application, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using our websites, applications or services you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. To find out more, see “How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps”, (located at www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/, or any other URL Google may provide from time to time).  
To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

****How to disable cookies****

You may be able to configure your browser or our website, application or service to restrict cookies or block all cookies if you wish, however if you disable cookies you may find this affects your ability to use certain parts of our website, applications or services. You can find more information about cookies and instructions on how to adjust your browser settings to accept, delete or reject cookies at the www.allaboutcookies.org website.

### **3\. Your Control Over Your Data**

You may choose to use our website without entering any personally identifiable information, but many of the services will not be available. 

If you would like to have your information completely deleted from our system, you may delete your account along with all audio and transcriptions via our online portal. Go to “My Profile” and click the “Delete” button underneath “Delete Account”.  
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about discounts, new products or services, or changes to this Privacy Policy. 

### **4\. Your Access to Your Data**

You can do the following at any time on our online portal:

> – See what personal data we have about you, if any.  
>  – Change or delete any personal data we have about you  
>  – Delete your audio files  
>  – Delete your transcription output 

If you would like to express any concern you have about our use of your data, you may contact us via the email address or phone number given on our website and at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. 

### **5\. Securing Your Data**

When you submit sensitive information via our website, it is protected both online and offline. The collection of sensitive information (such as credit card data) is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. We strive to keep your personally identifiable information secure, however please note that no security measures are absolute. Thus, we cannot guarantee that your personal data will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. We will make reasonable attempts to notify you within 72 hours if we determine that TranscribeMe has experienced a security breach and there is a reasonably likely risk of identity theft, or where otherwise required by law.

In addition to security information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only associates who need access to personally identifiable information are granted it. Our servers and databases that process and store personally identifiable information are kept in a secured environment.

### **6\. Contacting Us**

If you feel that we are not abiding by this Privacy Policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1-800-275-5513 or via email at [hello@transcribeme.com](mailto:hello@transcribeme.com).

### **Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will update the Policy modification date below. This Policy was last modified on the 23rd of May, 2018.
